Ritesh

Mobile No: 8700199377 | Email: riteshdhondhale@gmail.com | LinkedIn: ritesh112

SUMMARY:

Front-end developer with enthusiastic in creating immersive and intuitive web experiences that resonate with users and contribute to the success of digital products and services. Expanding my full-stack development skills and fueling my daily growth as a programmer.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

Frontend: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Figma, Webflow, WordPress

■ Backend: C#, .Net Framework

Database: SQL Server

Design: Photoshop, Illustrator

EXPERIENCE:

Junior Engineer Technical Support - iEnergizer Ltd. | Sept 2023 - April 2024

- Provided first-line technical support to internal and external users via phone, email, and live chat.
- Troubleshooted and resolved various technical issues related to software applications, hardware components, and network connectivity.
- Developed clear and concise explanations of technical solutions for users with varying technical expertise.
- Documented support interactions and solutions to improve the knowledge base for future reference.

Customer Service Representative - Caretel Infotech Ltd. | Jan 2019 - Oct 2019

- Effectively manage customer inquiries and complaints, adeptly offering solutions to resolve their issues.
- Prioritized delivering top-tier services to ensure optimal customer satisfaction while cultivating enduring and positive relationships with the company.

Customer Service Associate – WHSmith Retail Pvt. Ltd. | July 2017 – Feb 2018

- Enhanced the customer experience by warmly welcoming patrons, providing informative responses to inquiries, and skillfully handling financial transactions.
- Proactively drove sales by engaging with customers and sharing expert product knowledge.
- Maintained the store's cleanliness and impeccable condition while contributing to efficient inventory management

PROJECTS:

Portfolio

Tech Stack: HTML and Tailwind CSS

A portfolio site built with HTML, JavaScript and Tailwind CSS

EDUCATION:

Indira Gandhi Nation Open University, Delhi | Bachelor's Degree in Computer Application